{
    "id": "3820e317091743788491dc20d27d620e",
    "title": "Confusing Words Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He is a …..................... . Catholic.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "devote",
                "devout"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She has .....................… her life to helping the poor and the sick.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "devoted",
                "devouted"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "God is very …..................... ..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "graceful",
                "gracious"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You can eat carrots cooked or .......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "row",
                "raw"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He .....................….. in sports.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "excels",
                "exciles"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "His good works need to be .....................….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "commended",
                "commented"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The mother ..................... . the weeping child.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "concealed",
                "consoled"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "English literature is full of ..................... to Greek and Latin authors.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "illusions",
                "allusions"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Though he is sixteen, he is very .....................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "childlike",
                "childish"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I was impressed by her .....................…… simplicity.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "childlike",
                "childish"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}